[show]
Press "Space" to continue.[w]
Flower is a KrKr-like dialog system for Unity.[lr]
You can use commands to trigger some functions like showing image, playing audio, controlling progress in the plain text.[w]

You can use [[l] to wait for user press![l] And it will continue the dialogs.[w]
You can use [[r] to change the line![r]And it will continue the dialogs.[w]
You can use [[c] to clean up the line![c]And it will continue the dialogs.[w]
You can use [[lr] to wait for user press![lr]And it will change the line and continue the dialogs.[w]
You can use [[w] to wait for user press![w]The previous text will be erased and continue the dialogs.[w]
And you can also define your own special chars into the function map[UsageCase,2,3].[w]
You can use [[hide] to hide the dialog[l][hide][l], [show] use [[show] to show the dialog.[w]
...[w]......[w].........[w]

You can use [[stop] or call Stop function to stop the system, [r]
and call Resume function to resume the progress.[w]
Press "R" to resume the system.[stop] Nice![w]
With stop and resume, you can integrate with your gameplay system.[w]
You can setup buttons easily by calling "SetupButtonGroup" and "SetupButton" with your customized callback functions.[w]
If you want to show variables in this the dialog or using variables in commands or effects, you can use "SetVariable" to set up the key and the value of variable.[w]
And using [[#YOUR_VARIABLE_NAME] to show the value.[w]
My name is : [#MyName] [w]
Also, you can apply <b>rich text</b> in the <color=#4fe866ff><size=100>flower</size></color> <i><color="red">system</color></i>.[w]
Use [[wait,3000] to wait [wait,3000]3 sec, you can also modify the waiting seconds.[w]
...[w]......[w].........[w]
